http://www.metrokitchen.com/faq_help

Tap to Receive Deal Notifications
Enter your email address to receive your deal notifications.
Frequently Asked Questions
How do I return something?
+
Items purchased from MetroKitchen can be returned or exchanged if they are in new and unused condition within 30 days of receipt. Click here for more information.
How quickly will you ship my order?
+
We maintain a huge inventory in our Atlanta warehouse and most of our orders are sent from our warehouse the next business day. Some items including certain Enclume, John Boos, Capresso, Emile Henry, Fissler, Cristel, Dansk and Amoretti brother are shipped directly by the manufacturer and generally take 7-10 business days to ship. Shipping times are listed on each product page.
Most items on our site are in stock and ship out of our warehouse within one business day. However some items are out of stock and may take up to 4 weeks for delivery. If an item is out of stock it will most likely be indicated next to the item that is out of stock. There is a very small chance that an item that shows up in stock may actually be out of stock (Because someone may order the last of an item at the same time you are trying to order the same item or because of human error). We recommend that if you are ordering a large quantity of the same item, call us to find out if we can ship them all within a business day.
What if I need to change or correct a shipping address?
+
If you need to change the shipping address after your order has left our warehouse, please contact us immediately at (866) 276-4550 or at cs@metrokitchen.com. We will be happy to request a "delivery intercept/address change" with UPS/Fedex. Because UPS and Fedex now charge MetroKitchen $11 for each address change, we will pass that charge onto you. You will see a separate charge on your credit card for $11 when you request an address change or an address correction. Please note that we ship within 24 business hours or LESS and frequently orders leave our warehouse the same day as we receive them. It's critical for you to contact us as soon as you realize that an address needs to be changed.
If your order is returned to us due to an address error, an incomplete address or if no one is available to sign for an order above $1,000, we will be happy to reship your order to the correct address or to a different address. However, MetroKitchen is charged a minimum of $11 for re-shipping by UPS/Fedex. We will pass that charge onto you and charge your credit card for $11 in the event of an address problem resulting in a re-shipment back to MetroKitchen.
Do you actually stock the items on your website?
+
Yes! We have a warehouse chock-full of the top brands you want.
Do you collect sales tax?
+
No, except for shipments to addresses in the state of Georgia, as required by law.
Do you accept checks?
+
No.
What is your company's privacy policy?
+
Our privacy policy is simple: We will never sell or give your personal information to other companies for their marketing use.
Is your site secure?
+
Yes. Our site uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) to encrypt your credit card number and other personal information. SSL is the standard method for secure online transactions used at all major websites. When you begin the process of "checking out" of our shopping cart, you will be taken to a secure SSL page to enter your personal information. We are certified by the Better Business Bureau
Why do I need to enter my credit card number every time I place a new order on your website? Why doesn't your website remember who I am?
+
As a security measure, we do not store any credit card information on our web server. This means that our repeat customers have to enter their personal information every time they place an order. The advantage of this policy is that your credit card number can never be stolen from our web server, because it simply isn't there. We know it's a bit inconvenient for our valued customers, but the privacy and security of all our customers is a top concern.
